<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>Adelaide .NET User Group Podcast</title>
    <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/</link>
    <description>Recordings of presentations made at monthly meetings of the Adelaide .NET User Group</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Adelaide .NET User Group</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain for Mobile with Michael Williams</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 May 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/250152964/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://archive.org/download/201805b/2018%2005b.mp3</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201805b/2018%2005b.mp3" length="18152909" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Blockchain is the next big thing, have you ever wondered how we can incorporate this technology with mobile?

In this session, we will learn how to integrate blockchain technology with your mobile applications, and have a look at the new Azure Blockchain Workbench]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming in Microsoft Visual F# with Stephen Hosking</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 May 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/250152964/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://archive.org/download/201805a/2018%2005a.mp3</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201805a/2018%2005a.mp3" length="15443667" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[F# is the third major language in .Net. It is a functional, object-oriented language suitable for most applications, and shines in large and/or technical projects.

There will be a coding demonstration and pragmatic pointers for getting started and progressing to real world projects]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Firebase to quickly build useful software that can scale, with Darren Neimke</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/249380900/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://archive.org/download/201804b/2018%2004b.mp3</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201804b/2018%2004b.mp3" length="12287979" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Firebase is an easy to use set of technologies that help us rapidly build and deploy applications. It follows a reactive approach, using Observables to supply realtime updates whenever data changes. In this talk, Darren takes us through the Firebase ecosystem, and explains how it can be used to build an Angular web application. Throughout the talk we will learn about the Firebase NoSQL data stores, how to implement security, and we will deploy an application using the Firebase CLI tooling.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's new in the OWASP Top 10, with Jim Burger</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/249380900/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://archive.org/download/201804a/2018%2004a.mp3</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201804a/2018%2004a.mp3" length="20813320" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[OWASP recently updated their top 10 web application development recommendations. I'll walk through some of the new items in the Top 10, and discussing their implications and ways to address them.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Docker and ASP.NET Core 2.0 with Jack Ni</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/248320134/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/248320134/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201803_201806/2018%2003.mp3" length="17104394" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Learn about using Docker with ASP.NET Core, Docker Compose. Find out about ASP.NET Core's built in dependency injection support. Also see how to use Swagger 2.0 with API versioning.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating to Git and VSTS with David Gardiner</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/247505479/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://archive.org/download/201802b/2018%2002b.mp3</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201802b/2018%2002b.mp3" length="23035054" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[How does a team successfully move from an internally-hosted centralized version control system to Git running in Visual Studio Team Services? Hear how one group of developers did this by taking along the people, adapting their processes, embracing the technology, in a culture open to change.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-grid Peak PoE Systems with Ewan Parsons</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/247505479/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/247505479/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201802_20180218/2018%2002.mp3" length="18060899" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Learn about the new 60W Power over Ethernet standard, and how you can save up to 30% on power using demand-response programs.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Serverless with Azure Functions, with Sam Fernando</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/246442328/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/246442328/</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[The way systems are hosted are changing day by day and Azure serverless technologies make it easier for us to focus on the business logic and not worry about the underlying hosting and management. Azure functions assist with transitioning from monolithic software architectures to micro services patterns while providing the same experience for developers and administrators.

Sam Fernando will step us through the basics of Azure Functions, how to develop and host functions and few integration scenarios with popular SaaS services.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build automation with Cake</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/244245302/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/244245302/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/BuildAutomationWithCake/201712.mp3" length="17434074" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Do you have a complex build process? Is your CI build not quite the same as building locally? Can you grab a fresh copy of the source code and be up and running in minutes?

Cake is a build automation system based on C#. Find out how you can use Cake to orchestrate the entire build process, from compiling, testing, package and deployment. By using C# as the build DSL, you'll feel instantly at home!

Hear about David's experiences moving from a traditional multi-step CI build process to driving the build entirely with Cake. See how you can make use of Cake's impressive built in functions and 3rd-party add-ins.

Learn how to leverage Cake's extension model to write your own addins to provide custom functionality.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Microsoft Bot Framework with Sam Fernando</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/243797389/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/243797389/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201710_201802/2017%2010.mp3" length="18375795" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Do you know that you can book your flights via Skype? SkyScanner has a bot for Skype, where you can book your next holiday via chat. You may even use the Advertiser Bot through Facebook to get your daily news digest. Bots are even making enterprises be efficient and productive by letting you focus on what you do best and let the Bot do the grunt work.

Bots are not new, but they are becoming more powerful, pervasive and acceptable in today’s society as a way to get answers, access information, buy goods and request for services. Not only chatting or texting, you could also be talking to a Bot via connectors like Cortana too.

Sam Fernando will step us through the basics of the Microsoft Bot Framework, developing bots, hosting in Azure and connecting with channels like Facebook, Skype and Cortana.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure API Management with Bill Chesnut</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 Aug 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/242028108/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/242028108/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201708_20170820/2017%2008.mp3" length="29318383" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Bill will be discussing and demonstrating the features Azure API Management. Looking at the Publisher/Azure Portal, Developer Portal and demonstrating API import and the power of the API Management Policies. Bill will also discuss the different usage scenarios and benefits of Azure API Management of both Web Application and Hybrid Integration.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Cognitive Services with Paul Usher</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/241185386/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/241185386/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201707_20170820/2017%2007.mp3" length="22196243" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Just the words "Cognitive Services" can be daunting, but it doesn't need to be! In fact, what if I said you can spin up a speech to text engine that will analyse the output and tell you the sentiment behind what it contains... in under 15 minutes. That is exactly what will be shown in this session - by creating a simple application that can consume an audio file (mp3) and use the power of Azure Cognitive Services to do the rest. There are many aspects to ACS and you'll be pleasantly surprised at how easy it is to integrate into existing processes.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xamarin Forms Deep Dive with Sean Rodda</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/240131745/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/240131745/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201706_20170820/2017%2006.mp3" length="19325668" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Xamarin Forms is a framework that allows developers to easily create cross platform production ready apps. Sean will take you through the process of creating an application using Xamarin Forms with the backend of Azure Cosmos DB. 
Recently at the Build developer conference, Microsoft announced some great improvements to the Xamarin platform including Xamarin Live Player - a new way continuously deploy and debug application directly on iOS and Android. Sean will show you how easy it is to set up Xamarin Live Player, allowing you to easily view your UI changes without the annoyance of having to rebuild and redeploy to your device.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software architecture with David Rogers</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/239562095/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/239562095/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201705_20170528/2017%2005.mp3" length="18925485" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[A code-centric discussion on building a framework for an enterprise application, using an "onion"-style architecture.

Light on diagrams, heavy on demos, this presentation will show how we can tie together some really handy open source libraries to form a framework which lends itself to writing maintainable, production-grade code. Such libraries include FluentValidation, Automapper, log4net, MediatR, SimpleInjector and (of course) JSON.NET. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reality Check - HoloLens 101 with Bronwen Zande</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 8 Mar 2017 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/237629262/#Bronwen</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/237629262/#Bronwen</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/20170302_201704/2017%2003%2002.mp3" length="22636257" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Reality – Virtual, Augmented and Mixed. Join Bronwen – Microsoft Emerging Experiences MVP and get your reality in check.

This session will cover the different types of reality experiences and focus on the mixed reality of HoloLens. Bronwen will show you the actual device and how you can start building amazing holographic experiences for this self contained device. Don’t have a device – we’ll cover how you can start today without one. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Load Testing with Ben Laan</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 8 Mar 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/237629262/#Ben</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/237629262/#Ben</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/20170301_201704/2017%2003%2001.mp3" length="21394916" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[A demonstration of how to do performance testing with Visual Studio Load and Web Test Tools.We'll also investigate and compare open source and non-MS tools in this space, as well as a brief look at strategies for dealing with performance problems in web applications.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VS 2017 and Connect() Event Highlights with David Gardiner</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/235775147/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/235775147/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201612_20161227_2318/2016%2012.mp3" length="14576330" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Microsoft made some huge product announcements in New York recently. In this talk we'll show off some of the new features coming in Visual Studio 2017 including:

• Live Unit Testing

• Debugging improvements

• Docker integration

• Installer and setup improvements

• Performance improvements

as well as reviewing the changes coming in .NET, .NET Core,  Azure and SQL Server.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you hack it? Unbreakable Data Security (+ Hackathon) with Stav Morris </title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/234638412/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/234638412/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201610_20161027/2016%2010.mp3" length="23798538" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Stav and the team from A Backbone Solutions join us this month to talk about their unique approach to data security. There will be hardware to play with too. Can you hack the 'unhackable'?

We'll start with a short introduction into the philosophies of “unhackable” and “unbreakable”, and relate that to existing technologies, Blockchain and our own tech. Reviewing the logical breakdown of data ownership, and how it is important to storage and access concepts. The audience will be encouraged to participate throughout the talk; we want it to be a Socratic-type lecture. After this discussion, the audience can then decide whether to talk about logic or application.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Development -&gt; File | New | What Now??? with Paul Usher</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/233908316/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/233908316/</guid>
      <category>Podcast</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201609_20160917/2016%2009.mp3" length="19734204" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Join Microsoft MVP & DevExpress Technical Evangelist Paul Usher, as he takes a look at the state of play for desktop development. During this frank session you will see where technologies like Electron fit into the picture, which technology should you reach for when starting a new desktop project? WinForms? WPF? Electron?  Should you be targeting xplat? Is .NET Core the next big thing? Can devices like the Raspberry Pi replace some desktop functionality? It’s set to spark some interesting discussions and is one meeting not to be missed! (evening proudly sponsored by DevExpress)

About Paul

Paul Usher is a Technical Evangelist at DevExpress. DevExpress technologies help software developers build high-performance business solutions, see complex software with greater clarity, increase productivity, and create stunning applications for Windows® and the Web in the shortest possible time.

Prior to joining DevExpress, Paul ran (and still owns) an independent software development company which specialises in custom solutions for small to medium businesses, with a focus on mobile and paperless solutions. He has developed more than 100 commercial applications on Windows, OS X, iOS, and other platforms that are used worldwide covering a wide range of industries from retail, medical, construction, and various service industries. Paul is a published author, WintellectNOW instructor and speaks at industry events around the world. His blog is available at paulusher.info]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoT, Node + Cloud AND Parallel Programming Design Patterns and Considerations</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/232881078/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/232881078/</guid>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201608_20160917/2016%2008.mp3" length="116222292" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[<SPAN class=full>
<p><B>IoT, Node.js (visual/flow coding) + Cloud with Jack Ni</B> <br/></p>
<p>This talk will cover:</p>
<p>•&nbsp;What is IoT?</p>
<p>•&nbsp;A background history of embedded systems to IoT <br/></p>
<p>• What are the challenges</p>
<p>• What tools can be used</p>
<p>• Cloud with IoT, and why we need cloud</p>
<p>• Demos</p>
<p><I><B>About Jack</B></I></p>
<p>Highly skilled in the field of enterprise software solution development, mobile app (Xamarin) development , IoT(Raspberry/WinCE) development and delivery, Jack is currently working on a working on a business solution involving Raspberry Pi, Mobile app Dev using Xamarin and Azure Cloud. <br/></p>
<OL></OL>
<p><B>Parallel Programming Design Patterns and Considerations with "Curious" George Georgiou</B> <br/></p>
<p>A taste of some design patterns, techniques and things to consider in order to increase throughput of your applications and large data processing systems with the tools available in the .NET framework.</p>
<p><B><I>About George</I></B></p>
<p>An Adelaide developer who loves .net, LINQ, computers, 3D graphics and has more than enough things he's interested in to keep him from being bored well past his 70s and by then there will most likely be even more "things to poke around with" on his to do list </p></SPAN>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript : more than just another JS transpiler AND VS Team Services </title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 8 Jun 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/231160074/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/231160074/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/231160074/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201606_20160618/2016%2006.mp3" length="48330453" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is a recording of our June 2016 meeting. First up, we have our regular What's New segment with Ryan Spears. The main speaker for this month was Basarat Ali Syed presenting on TypeScript. Basarat's presentation is also available on YouTube under the title "Adelaide .NET User Group - TypeScript with Basarat". Wrapping up this recording is an update on the latest features in Visual Studio Team Services.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and release applications using VSTS/TFS 2015 Update 2 with Anthony Borton</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/230453148/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/230453148/</guid>
      <comments>http://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/230453148/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/201605_20160519_1000/2016%2005.mp3" length="30896404" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is a recording of our May 2016 meeting. First up we have a short demo from Shamsul Arifin on his Bengali language Text to Speech web app. Following this we have Anthony Borton on Build and release your applications using VSTS/TFS 2015 Update 2.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Encryption using .Net and SQL Server AND Building an Army of $10 Robots with HTML 5 and NodeJS</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/229525766/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/229525766/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/229525766/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/201604_201605/2016%2004.mp3" length="36710386" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[This is a recording of our April 2016 meeting. First up, we have our regular What's New segment with Ryan Spears, then we have two presentations. The first is from Duncan Greaves about "Data Encryption using .Net and SQL Server", and then finally we have Dr Tom Tilley on "Building an Army of $10 Robots with HTML 5 and Node.js"]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Octopus Deploy with David Rogers</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 Mar 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228863602/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228863602/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228863602/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podcastgarden.com/login/audio-13/13279/ADNUGMeeting2016-03.mp3" length="133221479" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying Enterprise Applications can be an art unto itself. Sophisticated, distributed systems often have a lot of moving parts. Databases often need to be updated with schema changes and new reference data with each new release.

Octopus Deploy takes a lot of the heavy lifting out of complex deployments. Being an automated process, it removes opportunities for human error to occur during a deployment. It also integrates well with Continuous Integration servers, resulting in end-to-end automation from code commits to deployment of compiled code.

In this presentation, we'll take a look at the basics of Octopus Deploy and see how it can significantly free up developers to focus on actual development, rather than having to also worry about the deployment aspects as well.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Reality in .NET with Matthew Wilson</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228144620/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228144620/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/228144620/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podcastgarden.com/login/audio-13/13279/ADNUGMeeting2016-02.mp3" length="104287081" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[In this presentation we’ll take a look at virtual reality technology with a focus on how to develop software using the .net stack. We’ll look back at the early days of the technology and some of the impressive accomplishments and failures of those attempts at creating virtual reality. We’ll then fast forward twenty years to review the current state of the art and some of the exciting recent developments.

Knowing where we currently stand with the hardware we’ll delve into how to write software for virtual reality using .NET. We’ll take a look at the tools used and the familiar (and not so familiar) programming principles required when developing for virtual reality.

The presentation will include code examples and of course there will be an Oculus Rift on standby with several VR applications from Novus Res ready to be experienced.
]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliTest and other unit testing tools</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/227689829/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/227689829/</guid>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podcastgarden.com/login/audio-13/13279/IntelliTestandOtherTestingTools.mp3" length="91790418" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA['IntelliTest' is one of the new features that shipped in Visual Studio 2015. This talk will demonstrate IntelliTest and see how it is particularly useful for creating tests for legacy code. But you don't have to just stick with what's in the box - we'll also update you on a number of other unit testing tools and libraries that can make writing unit tests easier. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Dive into Creating API Apps and Logic Apps with Bill Chesnut</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 Dec 2015 04:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/226664385/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/226664385/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/226664385/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <description><![CDATA[This session will take a developer and architect through the steps to create complex Logic Apps with non-connector API Apps and leveraging the numerous existing connector API Apps. Attendee will learn how to use Azure Services Bus Connector, File Connector, Office 365 Connector and custom API Apps in a Logic App, which will include conditional logic, retry logic and error handling. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buddy IoT Platform AND Web Accessibility</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225603993/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225603993/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225603993/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podcastgarden.com/login/audio-13/13279/ADNUGMeeting-2015-11.m4a" length="46143055" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Buddy IoT Platform 
Buddy is a cloud platform for Internet of Things (IoT). Using Buddy, you can collect all of your device data with a single, clean API and send it to any analytics, marketing or visualization tool or service.

In this presentation, Habib Heydarian will provide an overview of the Buddy platform, explain how to use the Buddy API to build Internet of Things applications and describe the features & capabilities of the platform.

Web Accessibility

Accessibility is something we should all care about. Even if it doesn't affect you individually now, chances are you know someone who does (or even yourself as we all get older and our senses become less effective than they used to be) having accessible software becomes essential.

Cliff Edwards give a practical overview of making the web more accessible. He debunks common myths, highlights pitfalls and demonstrates tools and techniques to make the web a more accessible place for everyone. ]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Azure Explained with Paul Usher</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225527001/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225527001/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/225527001/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.org/download/ADNUGMeeting201510/ADNUG%20Meeting%202015-10.mp3" length="33707799" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[The thing about Azure, as with any cloud service, is understanding what is available.  Join Paul Usher as he takes us through the most common uses of Azure, Web, Mobile, Data.  In this session Paul will show just how quickly you can get up to speed with Microsoft’s cloud offerings, as well as creating database, blob storage and building a simple yet powerful website in VS and deploying with a few clicks.  You can also see some of the other features of Azure at work.  Fast paced, lots to see and learn and of course always room for some fun.]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio 2015 and Roslyn</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 9 Sep 2015 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/224845803/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/224845803/</guid>
      <comments>https://www.meetup.com/Adelaide-dotNET/events/224845803/</comments>
      <category>Podcasts</category>
      <enclosure url="http://www.podcastgarden.com/login/audio-13/13279/ADNUGMeeting-2015-09.mp3" length="263768229" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Studio 2015 Launch

Ryan and Dave go through what's new in Visual Studio 2015. Be there early for official VS 2015 'swag' giveaways.

There’s something about Roslyn

Ben Laan on Rosyln, Microsoft’s .NET Compiler Platform ‘As a Service’. This presentation attempts to answer the what, why and how of Roslyn with a high-level dip into Microsoft’s next generation C# (and VB.NET) compiler.
Topics include Rosyln Overview Features and Benefits, some demos to show - Code as Data, Visual Studio Integration, Code Generation/Conversion and possibly some other interesting things along the way! ]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>